别再争了好吗? 这又没什么大不了的
Let it go. It's not a big deal.
没什么大不了?这简直是太神奇了 你够到之后，把它扯下来
Not a big deal? It's amazing. You reach in,there's one maneuver and bam!
胸罩就从袖子出来了
A bra. Right out the sleeve.
据我所知，男生可没有那样简单的事情 对不对?
As far as I know,guys don't do anything that comes close. Right?
拜托，男生可以站着尿
Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
我们行吗?我倒要试试看
We can? Okay,I'm trying that.
知道什么最令我嫉妒?
Know what blows my mind?
女人随时都可以看自己的胸部
Women can see breasts anytime they want.
低头一看…它就在那里
You look down,and there they are.
真搞不懂你们怎么会有心工作
How you get any work done is beyond me.
知道我搞不懂什么吗? 男人可以做许多下流的事…
I don't get how guys can do so many mean things...
…却能毫不在乎
...and not even care.
多重性高潮  没错
-Multiple orgasms! -There you go.
六人行 第1季 第05集 洗衣服
The One With the East German Laundry Detergent
了不起,周末夜,重要的夜晚
Saturday night. The big night!
约会的夜晚…周末夜…
Date night! Saturday night. Saturday night!
- 没有计划是吗? - 一个都没有
-No plans,huh? -Not a one!
连和珍妮丝分手的打算都没有?
Not even breaking up with Janice?
对…闭嘴
Right,right. Shut up.
钱德，没有人喜欢分手
Chandler,nobody likes breaking up with someone.
凯文・米勒除外，愿他在地狱里烂掉
Except for Kevin Millmore,may he rot in hell.
-你明白的 -我知道,但是这确实太难了
-You just gotta do it. -I know. But it's just so hard.
你坐在她身旁…而她却一无所知
You're sitting there with her. She has no idea.
最后你鼓起勇气
You finally get up the courage to do it.
在这实在尴尬的时刻 当你将纸条拿给她
There's that awkward moment when you've handed her the note.
在她看完纸条之前,你尝试着跑出饭店
You try to run out of the restaurant before she's finished the note.
干嘛分手?…像个男人样，不再打电话就行了
Why do you have to break up with her? Be a man. Just stop calling.
如果愿意，我和你一起做
If you want,I'll do it with you.
谢了，但这样她会认为 我们是联手来对付她
She'd feel like we're ganging up on her.
你和珍妮丝分手 我和东尼分手
You dump Janice,I'll dump T ony.
-东尼?你要和东尼分手? -他人很好.但是我对他再没新鲜感了
-You're breaking up with T ony? -He's sweet,but it's not fun anymore.
我不知道问题是在于我 还是他的绝食抗议
I don't know if it's me or his hunger strike,I don't know.
还有人需要什么吗?
Do you want anything else?
你做了有核果，巧克力之类的派…
You had a nutty,chocolate-y,kind of cake-y,pie thing that
没事，我还好
Nothing. I' m fine.
怎么啦,怪怪的
What's wrong? Why so scrunchie?
是我爸…他要买奔驰敞篷车给我
My father wants to give me a Mercedes convertible.
那家伙真叫我生气
That guy,he burns me up.
如果想要奔驰我就得搬回家了
Yeah,it's a Mercedes if I move back home.
太可恶了…他称我为“年轻的女士”
It was horrible! He called me "young lady. "
我最受不了我爸这样叫我
I hate when my father calls me that.
他是不是又说你年纪太轻之类
Did he say "You' re not up to this" again?
对,他在这次加长版中说了三次…
I got the extended version with choruses of...
…“你不可能独立”
... "You'll Never Make it on Your Own. "
嘿,乔伊
Hi,Joey.
天呀,安吉拉
Oh,my God! Angela!
被你甩掉对她大有好处
Wow! Being dumped by you agrees with her.
-你想过去吗? -不,是的，不
-Are you gonna go over there? -No. Yeah. No.
不,我不.我不想显得太渴望了
Okay,but not yet. I don't wanna seem too eager.
一个密西西比,两个密西西比
One Mississippi,two Mississippi...
…三个密西西比.那看起来真酷
...three Mississippi. That seems pretty cool.
-安吉拉 -乔伊
-Hey,Angela. -Joey.
你看起来不错
You look good.
因为我的衣服突显出我的胸部
That's because l' m wearing a dress that accents my boobs.
看得出来
You don't say.
瑞秋，你今晚有何节目?
So,Rachel,what are you doing tonight?
精彩丰富，我要和莫妮卡去洗衣店
Big glamour night. Me and Monica at Launderama.
想知道有个巧合吗? 猜猜谁也要去洗衣店?
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence? Guess who's doing laundry there too?
-谁? -我
-Who? -Me!
难道还不够清楚?
Was that not clear?
何不…
Why don't...?
何不让我加入你们?
Why don't I just join you both there?
你的公寓没有洗衣间吗?
Don't you have a laundry room in your building?
是的
Yes.
有，我的公寓有洗衣间
I do have a laundry room in my building.
但是现在有老鼠了
But there's a rat problem.
它们显然对烘干机里的香料纸感兴趣
Apparently,they're attracted to dryer sheets.
进入时还好 出来时却毛绒绒的
They're going in fine,but they're coming out all fluffy.
-7点左右见? -好的
-Anyway,7-ish? -Sure.
-免了,我现在和鲍伯交往 -鲍伯?谁是鲍伯?
-Forget it. I' m with Bob now. -Bob? Who the hell's Bob?
鲍伯简直是棒透了 聪明，成熟，又有真正的工作
Bob is great. He's smart,sophisticated,and he has a real job.
你每个月面试三次就称自己是演员 但是鲍伯
You go on three auditions a month and you' re an actor. Bob
我们在一起时很开心
Come on! We were great together.
不只是寻欢作乐我们也聊得来
And not just at the fun stuff,but,like,talking too.
抱歉,乔伊 你曾说我们当朋友就好,那么
Sorry,Joey. You said," Let's be friends. " So guess what?
-什么? -我们只是朋友
-What? -We' re just friends.
行
Fine. Fine.
我们四个何不一起出去吃晚饭? 就像朋友一样
Why don't the four of us have dinner tonight? As friends.
哪四个?
What "four of us"?
你和鲍伯,我和我的女友…
You and Bob,and me and my girlfriend...
…莫妮卡
... Monica.
要我说,这小伙绝对适合你
I' m telling you,this guy's perfect for you.
算了吧,从你那打嗝会嗝出字母表的表兄后 我再也不敢了
Forget it! Not after your cousin who could belch the alphabet.
没骗你，他真的很棒 他叫鲍伯，安吉拉的…
Come on,this guy's great. His name's Bob. He's Angela's...
…哥哥 鲍伯简直是太棒了 聪明，成熟
... brother. He's smart,he's sophisticated...
…又有真正的工作
...and he has a real job.
我呢?我每个月面试三次就称自己是演员
I go on three auditions a month and say l' m an actor,but he's
-上帝啊 -什么?
-God help us. -What?
丑陋的裸男在铺厨房瓷砖
Ugly Naked Guy is laying kitchen tile.
我在求你帮忙
Look,l' m asking a favor here.
如果我能为她哥哥做点事 或许她会回到我身旁
If I do this for her brother,maybe Angela will come back to me.
你是怎么了? 你和千百个女人约会
What's going on? You go out with tons of girls.
我知道,但是安吉拉很不一样
I know,but Angela's different.
她就像那一种…那种雪花或者…
She's like one of a kind,like a snowflake or....
-其他像雪花的东西？ -是的,是的
-Something else like a snowflake? -Yeah,yeah.
我犯了天大的错误 我不该和她分手
Look,I made a huge mistake. I never should've broke up with her.
愿意帮我吗?求求你
Will you help me? Please?
等等…你能不能不要碰其他的东西
Hold on a sec. You need to not touch any of those.
没问题，再见
Okay,bye.
莫妮卡不能去了 现在只剩我和瑞秋
Monica's not coming. It's just gonna be me and Rachel.
等等，老兄你确定自己仔细想过
Hold on,camper. You've thought this through?
只是去洗衣服，没仔细想过
It's laundry. The thinking-through is minimal.
你是说只有你和瑞秋? 只有你们两个?
Just you and Rachel? Just you two?
这叫约会 你们要去约会
This is a date. You're going on a date.
-我有一阵子没干这个了啊 -她都不知道能算是约会吗?
-I haven't done that in a while. -ls it a date if she doesn't know?
当然是的 星期六晚上，什么规则都可以用
Yes,absolutely. Saturday night,all rules apply.
你在说些什么呢? 该再刮刮胡子或挑瓶美酒?
What are you saying? I should shave again? Pick up some wine?
或许你该再考虑你那肮脏的内衣裤
Well,you may wanna rethink the dirty underwear.
因为她将首度见到你的内衣裤 想让她看见你那肮脏的内衣裤吗?
It's the first time she'll see your underwear. You want it dirty?
不想
No.
衣物柔顺剂也有问题
And the fabric softener?
我的熊宝贝柔顺剂又怎么了?
Okay,now what is wrong with my Snuggles?
这代表我敏感贴心
What? It says I'm a sensitive,warm kind of guy.
就像一只毛绒绒的熊宝贝
You know,like a little fuzzy bear.
-好吧，我会在路上买其他牌子 -这才对
-I'll pick something else up. -There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
鲍伯长什么样? 到底是高还是矮?
What does Bob look like? Is he tall,short?
-什么? -什么什么?
-Which? -Which what?
-你没和鲍伯见过面，对不? -对，可是…
-You've never met Bob,have you? -No,but
-拜托，这家伙可能相当… 嘿,乔伊
-For all we know,he's horribly -Hey,Joey!
非常的吸引人. 我闭嘴就是了
Horribly attractive. I'll be shutting up now.
他们在哪儿?他们在哪儿?
Where are they? Where are they?
感觉真好，我们俩从未独处过
This is nice. We never do anything,just the two of us.
对，或许明天 我们可以租辆车撞几只小狗
Great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent a car,run over some puppies.
我不想那样
I don't wanna do that.
-她来了 -祝你有个愉快的分手
-Here we go. -Have a good breakup.
-珍妮丝 -真高兴你打电话给我
-Hey,Janice. -My God,I am so glad you called me.
我从来没这么悲惨的一天
I had the most supremely awful day.
不妙
That's not good.
能端杯浓缩咖啡和拿铁来吗?
Can I get an espresso and a latte over here?
我们刚在有蔬菜的那个摄影小站拍了照 但那些蔬菜烂透了
We got the proofs from the shoot with the vegetables. They sucked.
我的整个下午就这样毁了 我去逛街购物
I blew off the afternoon. I went shopping.
然后就为你买…
And I got you....
我在找…我在找…
I'm looking. I'm looking.
我为你…
I' m looking.
-我为你… -什么?
-I got you -What?
-什么? -你帮我买什么?
-What? -What did you get me there?
我帮你买…
I got you...
…这个
...these.
驯鹿布威图案的袜子（《飞鼠洛基冒险记》中的动画角色）
Bullwinkle socks.
-真可爱 -我知道你已有松鼠洛基的了
-That's sweet. -I knew you had Rockys.
你可以穿一双布威的或穿一双洛基的,或混着穿
You can wear Bullwinkle and Bullwinkle or Rocky and Rocky,or you can mix.
驯鹿和松鼠，随你高兴
Moose and squirrel. Whatever you want.
我再去叫一杯浓缩咖啡 想再来一杯拿铁吗?
I'm gonna get another espresso. More latte?
不用了，我的还没喝完
No,l' m still working on mine.
-你这样就搞定了？ -是的，你知道这样做很难
-That's it? -Yeah,it was really hard.
-没错，那个拥抱真惨烈 -你又不是当事人
-Yeah,the hug looked pretty brutal. -You weren't there.
-对不起 -事情处理的怎样?
-Sorry. -How are things going?
怎样?还没有进展. 她给我买了袜子
Going? Things are not going. She got me socks.
可以配你的洛基了啊! 她真的很关心你,对不起
These go with your Rockys. She really cares about you l' m sorry.
借过，让开…
Coming through. Move. Move!
抱歉，我用这台洗衣机
Excuse me! I was kind of using that machine.
是吗?不过现在不是了
Yeah,well,now you' re kind of not.
但是我占位置了,我放了篮子在上面
But I saved it. I put my basket on top.
抱歉，这是你的篮子吗?
I'm sorry. Is that your basket?
真漂亮， 但是我没看到肥皂水
It's pretty. Unfortunately,I don't see suds!
什么?
What?
没肥皂水就不算保留，行吗?
No suds,no save,okay?
怎么了?
What's going on?
没什么 这个凶女人抢了我的洗衣机
Nothing. This horrible woman just took my machine.
你有把篮子放上面吗?
Was your basket on top?
-有，但是没有肥皂水? -然后呢?
-Yeah,but there were no suds. -So?
-没肥皂水就不算保留 -没肥皂水,抱歉
-You know,no suds,no save. -No suds,no Excuse me.
等等 这是我朋友用的机器
Hold on a second! This is my friend's machine.
她的东西没在里面
Hey,hey,hey! Her stuff wasn't in it!
你明知根本没这个规矩
Hey,hey,hey! That's not the rule,and you know it!
表演结束
All right. Show's over.
没什么好看的
Nothing to see here.
洗衣服吧
Okay. Let's do laundry.
这简直是太神奇了 我连汤都不敢退
That was amazing! I can't even send back soup.
因为你是个温柔可爱的
Well,that's because you' re such a sweet,gentle....
你?你? 你得用洗衣粉
Do you? Do you? Oh,hey. You must need detergent.
-那是什么? 乌伯怀斯
-What's that? -Uberweiss.
来自德国的新产品 洗净力超强
It's new. It's German. It's extra tough!
瑞秋，你不打算分开洗吗?
Rach,are you gonna separate those?
天哪,我像个洗衣大白痴
Oh,God. Am I being a total laundry spaz?
我得用一台洗衬衣 用另一台洗裤子吗?
Am I supposed to use one machine for shirts and another for pants?
你没洗过衣服?
Have you never done this before?
没有，但我认识这样洗过的人
Well,not myself. But I know other people that have.
好吧，被你说对了 我没洗过衣服
Okay. You caught me. I'm a laundry virgin.
别担心，我会用轻柔绞洗
Don't worry. I'll use the gentle cycle.
你得用一台洗你全部的白衣白衣
Basically,you wanna use one machine for all your whites.
另一台洗其他颜色的衣服
A whole other machine for your colors.
第三台洗…
And a third for your...
…贴身.胸罩和…
...delicates. That would be your bras...
…内裤之类的
...and your underpanty things.
这些棉质的白色内裤呢?
These are white cotton panties.
与白衣还是贴身衣物一起洗?
Would they go with whites or with delicates?
随便你
That would be a judgment call.
他好帅
He's so cute!
你们在哪儿长大?
Where did you grow up?
-布鲁克林 -克里佛兰
-Brooklyn Heights. -Cleveland.
-怎么会这样? -天哪!
-How'd that happen? -My God!
怎么了
What?
我突然感到一阵晕眩
I suddenly had the feeling I was falling.
但是没有
But I'm not.
你和安吉拉在一起?
So,you and Angela,huh?
-差不多 -你真幸运
-Yep. Pretty much. -You' re a lucky man.
知道我最想念她什么?
Know what I miss most about her?
她轻啃东西的声音
That cute nibbly noise she makes when she eats.
好像是快乐的小松鼠…
Like a happy little squirrel...
…或是鼬
...or a weasel.
-我倒是没注意过 -以后注意听
-I never really noticed. -Oh,yeah,yeah. Listen for it.
莫妮卡，莫妮卡很好
Monica. Monica is great.
没错
Yeah,she is.
不过不会维持很久
But it's not gonna last.
她要的太多了…在床上
She's too much for me in bed.
性方面的
Sexually.
我得告诉你,鲍伯简直是太棒了
I've gotta tell you,Bob is terrific.
可不是吗
Yeah,isn't he?
能遇上聪明幽默 心智年龄超过八岁的人真棒
It's great to meet a smart,funny guy who's emotionally older than 8.
知道吗?他在床上更是不可思议
You know what else? He's unbelievable in bed!
我哥从未跟我谈过 他何时失去他的第一次
My brother never even told me when he lost his virginity.
真好
That's nice.
你能办到的 这就像是拔创可贴一样
You can. It's like pulling off a Band-Aid.
快速拔起…露出伤口
Just do it really fast,and then the wound is exposed.
快去
Go! Go!
珍妮丝…
Hi,Janice.
我是说,我想我们不该再交往下去了
Here we go. I don't think we should go out anymore.
好的
All right.
我知道了…
Well,there you go.
停下来,停下来….
Stop it,stop it,stop it.
这和你无关
This isn't about you.
我知道,只是你害怕承诺
I know! It's about your fear of commitment.
我一点也不怕
I' m not afraid.
-拜托. -我不怕
-Please. -I don't!
-我不怕!我准备好了随时都可以承诺 -真的吗?
-I don't! I' m ready to commit anytime. -Really?
我知道这听起来很傻…
I know this is gonna sound stupid...
…但是我觉得如果我可以做这些
... but I feel that if I can do this...
…我想如果我可以自己洗衣服的话
...if I can actually do my own laundry...
…我就没有办不到的事
...there isn't anything I can't do.
我一点都不觉得傻
That does not sound stupid to me.
就像卡萝离开后,我第一次动手做晚饭
The first time I had to cook for myself after Carol left me
抱歉，时间到 接下来到我了
I'm sorry,that's all the time we have. Next on Ross....
怎么了?
-Uh-oh. -What?
衣服洗好了
Uh-oh....the laundry's done.
这是一首歌
It's a song.
我们唱的一首洗衣歌
The laundry song we sing.
衣服洗好了
Uh-oh! The laundry's done
-到底怎么了? -没事
-What's the matter? -Nothing.
衣服洗好了…
The laundry's done
罗斯，快给我看…
Come on,show me.
好吧，白衣中有一只红袜 所以白衣全变成…
It's just that you left a red sock with your whites,and now...
…全变成粉红色
...everything's kind of pink.
全变成粉红色?
Everything's pink?
对，但红袜还是红袜
Except for the red sock,which is still red.
抱歉，别伤心，任何人都可能发生这种事
Don't be upset. It can happen to anyone.
但是对我还是发生了
But it happened to me.
我穿这些看来会像一只棉花糖粉红猪
God,I'm gonna look like a big Marshmallow Peep!
我到底是怎么了?
What am I doing?
我爸说得对，我无法独立生活
My father's right! I can't live on my own.
我连洗衣服都不会
I can't even do laundry!
超狗（感恩节游行中的标志卡通形象）气球出了意外 它的头无法充气
Something went wrong with Underdog and they couldn't inflate his head.
于是…
So anyway...
…于是它的头就落在百老汇了
...his head is flopping down Broadway,right?
我心想这实在太不像话了
And I'm thinking how inappropriate this is.
有东西跑进我眼睛 能到灯下帮我看看吗?
Something's in my eye. Could we check it in the light,please?
-我的天呀! -怎么啦?
-Oh,my God! -What?
我们是坐在同一桌吗? 这就像是…
Were we at the same table? It's like...
…阿巴拉契亚的鸡尾酒会（太离谱了）
...cocktails in Appalachia.
-他们感情很好 -感情很好?她舌头都伸进了他的耳朵
-They' re close. -Close? Her tongue's in his ear.
你和罗斯就不会有小动作?
Like you've never got a little rambunctious with Ross.
乔伊，这令人太难受了，让人恶心
Joey,this is sick. It's disgusting. It's...
这不是真的，对不?
... not really true' is it?
谁说是真的?
Who's to say what's true?
-你到底在想什么? -好吧，我也不喜欢这样
-What were you thinking? -l' m not proud of this,okay?
或许有一点
Well,maybe I am a little.
-我要走了 -等等
-l' m out of here! -Wait!
你喜欢他,我要她,他喜欢你
You like him. I want her. He likes you.
-真的? -没错
-Really? -Yeah.
我想只要我们一起想办法
If we put our heads together,between the two of us...
就能让他们分开
...we can break them up.
真是抱歉没想到我会这样
I' m sorry. I can't believe I did this.
你的诺曼・梅勒（美国著名作家）的故事让我笑得嘴巴合不拢
I couldn't stop laughing at your Norman Mailer story.
服务生，再来一盘鸡翅
Waiter? One more plate of chicken wings over here.
我们是不同类型的人
Here's the thing. We're different.
我就好像丁丁丁 你就好像梆梆梆
I'm bing,bing,bing. You' re boom,boom,boom.
糟了，抱歉
Oh,my God! I' m so sorry!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事，只是我的隐形眼镜
It's just my lens. It's my lens.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我打中她的眼睛,眼睛
I hit her in the eye! In the eye!
这是有史以来世上最糟糕的分手
This is the worst breakup in the history of the world!
我的天
Oh,my God!
-你到底喝了几杯? -我也不知道,一百万杯?
-How many have you had? -I don't know. A million!
钱德，放轻松 快回到你的快乐天堂
Chandler,easy,easy. Go to your happy place.
-我没事的… -好吧
-l' m fine,l' m fine. -All right.
-不好，她回来了 -在这儿等着，深呼吸
-l' m not fine. Here she is. -Wait here,okay? Breathe.
-你是怎么办到的? -我有天赋
-How do you do that? -It's like a gift.
我每次分手都该找你
We should always break up together.
我乐意之至
I'd like that!
你已把衣服洗净了 这是最重要的
The clothes are clean. That's the important part.
大概吧…只是衣服都成了睡衣
I guess. Except everything looks like jammies now.
抱歉，推车本来是我们的
I'm sorry. Excuse me. We had this cart.
我的腰围本来是24寸 你丢东西了
I had a 24-inch waist. You lose things.
让开，别挡道
Now,come on. Get out of my way.
抱歉，或许我没说清楚 这车是我们的
I' m sorry. Maybe I wasn't being clear. This was our cart.
这上面没有衣服
There weren't clothes in it!
你又再乱编规定了
Hey,hey,hey,hey! Quit making up rules!
放手,车是我的
Let go! Come on,it's my cart.
好吧，想用这辆车
Listen,Mitzi,if you want it...
你就得推着我一起走
...you' re gonna have to take me with it!
-我赢了，看见没? -你真是太神奇了
-Yes! Did you see that? -You were incredible.
女士们先生们，一位脱胎换骨的新女性
A brand-new woman,ladies and gentlemen.
多亏了你我才能办到
Thank you. I could not have done this without you.
烘干机里还有衣服?
More clothes in the dryer?
-我没事,我没事 -你确定
-I'm fine. I'm fine. -Are you sure?
-你确定你没事 -是的
-Are you sure you' re okay? -Yeah.
-还疼吗? -是的
-Does it still hurt? -Yeah.
真是聪明，衣服颜色都很配 我也要这么做
What a neat idea! All your clothes match. I' m gonna do this.
-嘿,怎么样啦? -很好！
-How'd it go? -Excellent!
我们拆散那一对 并将他们占为已有
We ripped that couple apart and kept the pieces for ourselves.
真是美丽动人的故事
What a beautiful story.
-顺便说一下我没事. -对不起没注意
-I'm fine,by the way. -I'm sorry.
-钱德在哪儿? -他需要一点时间疗伤
-Where's Chandler? -He needed time to grieve.
我自由了…我自由了…
I' m free! I' m free!
他应该这么做
That ought to do it.